[
  {
    "question": "Contains part of the Andes mountain range",
    "answers": ["CL", "AR", "EC", "PE", "BO", "CO", "VE"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Contains part of the Himalayas mountain range",
    "answers": ["IN", "NP", "CN", "PK", "BT", "AF"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Contains part of the Rocky Mountains",
    "answers": ["US", "CA"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Contains part of the Alps mountain range",
    "answers": ["FR", "IT", "CH", "AT", "DE", "SI", "LI", "MC"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Contains part of the Amazon River",
    "answers": ["BR", "PE", "CO", "EC", "VE", "GY", "BO"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Contains part of the Nile River",
    "answers": [
      "EG",
      "SD",
      "ET",
      "UG",
      "KE",
      "TZ",
      "RW",
      "BI",
      "CD",
      "SS",
      "SD"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Contains part of the Mississippi River",
    "answers": ["US"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Contains part of the Yangtze River",
    "answers": ["CN"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Contains part of the Danube River",
    "answers": ["DE", "AT", "SK", "HU", "HR", "RS", "RO", "BG", "MD", "UA"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Contains part of the Ganges River",
    "answers": ["IN", "BD"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Contains part of the Caucasus Mountains",
    "answers": ["RU", "GE", "AM", "AZ"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Contains part of the Great Dividing Range",
    "answers": ["AU"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Contains part of the Volga River",
    "answers": ["RU"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Contains part of the Rhine River",
    "answers": ["DE", "CH", "FR", "NL", "LI", "AT"]
  }
]
